Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.thirt Mss.B.B61.inventory13
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents T
  - Tozzer, Alfred M. (Box 90-91)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 22
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 10
    - From Boas, 1911 May 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 26
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 July 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 6
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 16
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 29
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 13
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 25; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 19; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 26; 3p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 3; 3p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 19; 4p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 17; 3p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 19
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 17
    - From Boas, 1914 Apr. 17; 3p
    - From Boas, 1914 May 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 May 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 May 7
    - From Boas, 1914 May 23
    - From Boas, 1914 May 27
    - From Boas, 1914 June 30; 4p
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 28
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 30
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 19
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 21
    - From Boas, 1915 May 10
    - From Boas, 1915 May 28
    - From Boas, 1915 May 28
    - From Boas, 1915 July 15
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 28
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 30
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 3
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 7
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 2
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1916 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1916 May 3
    - From Boas, 1916 May 19
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - See Boas, F. (to Gordon, G.G.), 1916 May 22
    - From Boas, 1916 June 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 June 8
    - From Boas, 1916 June 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 June 9
    - From Boas, 1916 Sep. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 6
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 10
    - Nov.11 to Tozzer, Laufer, 1916 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 8
    - See Boas, F. (to Dixon, R.B.), 1916 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 31
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 May 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 May 5
    - From Boas, 1917 May 9
    - From Boas, 1917 May 9
    - From Boas, 1917 May 10
    - From Boas, 1917 May 19
    - From Boas, 1917 May 19
    - From Boas, 1917 May 21
    - From Boas, 1917 May 24
    - From Boas, 1917 June 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 June 14
    - From Boas, 1917 July 24
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 3
    - From Boas, 1917 Sep. 14
    - From Boas, 1917 Sep. 26
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 27; 6p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 9; 3p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Sep. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 30; 5p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug.?; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 12; 3p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p
    - Enc. Statement of Folk Lore Accounts, 1920 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 May 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Aug. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Sep. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 June 7; 1p
    - Enc. Tozzer, A.M. (in reply to above), 1928 June 21; 1p
    - Enc. Note from Tozzer in reply, 1928 Oct. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 23; 1p
    - To Tozzer, 1931 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Tozzer, 1931 July 13; 1p
    - To Tozzer, 1931 July 18; 1p
    - To Tozzer, 1931 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Tozzer, 1931 Dec. 8; 1p
    - To Tozzer, 1931 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 17; 3p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Sep. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 9; 3p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 4; 2p
    - Enc. with Boas, F. (to Kluckohn, C.), 1940 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1941 May 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Dec. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 May 25
    - To Boas, 1905 May 27
    - To Boas, 1905 June 3
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 7; 8p
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 29
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1908 May 1
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 May 12
    - To Boas, 1908 May 13
    - To Boas, 1908 May 20
    - To Boas, 1908 June 6
    - To Boas, 1908 June 11
    - To Boas, 1908 June 13
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1909 June 7
    - Found at end of Dec. 1909, 6p
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1911 May 27
    - To Boas, 1911 May 29
    - To Boas, 1911 May 29
    - To Boas, 1911 June 2
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 18; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 May 6
    - To Boas, 1912 July 27
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 8
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 25
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1913 July 1
    - To Boas, 1913 July 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 29
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 30
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 16
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 16; 5p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 25; 5p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 6; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 28; 6p
    - To Boas, 1914 May 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 May 11; 4p
    - To Boas, 1914 May 18; 4p
    - To Boas, 1914 May 24
    - To Boas, 1914 June 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 June 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 June 8
    - To Boas, 1914 June 10
    - To Boas, 1914 June 25
    - To Boas, 1914 July 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1914 July 14
    - To Boas, 1914 July 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 24
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 28
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 May 13
    - To Boas, 1915 May 26
    - To Boas, 1915 May 26
    - To Boas, 1915 May 26
    - To Boas, 1915 July 15
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 13
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 17
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 28
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 17
    - To Boas, 1916 May 9
    - To Boas, 1916 May 15
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 May 1
    - To Boas, 1917 May 8
    - To Boas, 1917 May 8
    - To Boas, 1917 May 12
    - To Boas, 1917 May 15
    - To Boas, 1917 May 19
    - To Boas, 1917 May 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 June 14
    - To Boas, 1917 June 16
    - To Boas, 1917 June 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 4
    - To Boas, 1917 Sep. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Sep. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Nov. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec. 12; 1p
    - Enc. see American Folk-lore Soc., 1919 Mar. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 21; 4p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 24; 1p
    - See: Boas, F. to Tozzer, A.M., 1919 Nov. 25
    - Found at end of Nov., 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 11; 1p
    - See Boas, F. to Tozzer, A.M., 1923 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 19; 1p
    - Enc. Tozzer, A.M. to Parsons, E.C., 1923 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 July 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 22; 2p
      - See carbon copy, 1928 June 9; 1p
      - See carbon copy, 1928 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 7; 1p
    - See carbon copy, 1929 Jan.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 16; 1p
      - See carbon copy, 1929 Dec.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1931 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 5; 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1931, 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1931, 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1931, 3p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 21; 1p
    - Enc. Tozzer, A.M. (to Keppel, F.F.), 1933 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 26; 3p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 5; 1p